Trust is a setup.
No Sudden Move is a crime, thriller film directed by Steven Soderbergh.
A group of criminals are brought together under mysterious circumstances and have to work together
to uncover what's really going on when their simple job goes completely sideways.
Curtis 'Curt' Goynes, played by Don Cheadle.
Ronald Russo, played by Benicio del Toro.
Matt Wertz, played by David Harbour.
Det. Joe Finney, played by Jon Hamm.
Frank Capelli, played by Ray Liotta.
Douglas 'Doug' Jones, played by Brendan Fraser.
No Sudden Move is a 2021 American crime thriller film directed by Steven
Soderbergh, produced by Casey Silver, and written by Ed Solomon.
The film features an ensemble cast including Don Cheadle, Benicio del Toro, David Harbour, Jon Hamm, Amy Seimetz, Brendan Fraser, Matt
Damon, Kieran Culkin, Noah Jupe, Craig Grant (in his final appearance), Julia Fox, Frankie Shaw, Ray Liotta, and Bill Duke.
No Sudden Move had its world premiere at the Tribeca Film Festival on June 18, 2021,
and was released in the United States on July 1, 2021, by HBO Max.
The film received positive reviews from critics with praise for
Soderbergh's direction and the performances of the cast.
The film explores themes of detective, safe, money, organized crime, gang.
The tone is intense.